<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[zero1fivehundred]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[zero1fivehundred]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/zero1fivehundred/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 20:32:29 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/zero1fivehundred/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tormenting the Grid]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Tormenting the Grid</h1><p>As you can tell, I've been tormenting the Grid AI with a barrage of different links. So far, it's handling them poorly. What this system needs is a curation function. Where humans can say "I like what you did there, keep that - and redesign that".</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/zero1fivehundred/tormenting-the-grid/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4dc77047-6bd8-4c24-a2cc-83ba3ac5f952</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 20:32:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Nine States of Design - The Startup]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Nine States of Design - The Startup</h1><p>Modern UI teams are designing components first; Interfaces are merely the thoughtful composition of components. This leaves an often glaring hole for users on "the unhappy path" - The places where users may, intentionally or not, stray from your idealized flow.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/aa38ae2593f0ba5c85ae0b08163cc6b340d953a4.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/zero1fivehundred/the-nine-states-of-design-the-startup/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f9fcdbe7-40b3-4b6c-ba0f-a040540dc293</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 20:28:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Do Things that Don't Scale]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Do Things that Don't Scale</h1><p>July 2013 One of the most common types of advice we give at Y Combinator is to do things that don't scale. A lot of would-be founders believe that startups either take off or don't. You build something, make it available, and if you've made a better mousetrap, people beat a path to your door as promised.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.paulgraham.com/ds.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b637a49c-74f0-45f4-94bb-06678523812d</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 19:48:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ursula K. Le Guin on Being a Man]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ursula K. Le Guin on Being a Man</h1><p>Who are we when we, to borrow Hannah Arendt's enduring words, "are together with no one but ourselves"? However much we might exert ourselves on learning to stop letting others define us, the definitions continue to be hurled at us - definitions predicated on who we should be in relation to some concrete or abstract other, some ideal, some benchmark beyond the boundaries of who we already are.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/77b607d680a8ee7d28a3795e61874a86741ce9a6.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.brainpickings.org/2014/10/17/ursula-k-le-guin-gender/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8efdb71d-1042-4404-a453-3e4d3281dc61</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 19:14:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The History Manifesto: How to Eradicate the Epidemic of Short-Termism and Harness Our Past in Creating a Flourishing Future]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The History Manifesto: How to Eradicate the Epidemic of Short-Termism and Harness Our Past in Creating a Flourishing Future</h1><p>I spend a significant amount of time on ideas at the intersection of the timeless and the timely, something I find to be of growing urgency in a culture such as ours, where the tyrannical reverse-chronology of newsfeeds implies that the latest, being literally at the top, is also of the greatest importance and meaning.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/c63d4609499ac59c77ff307c4046a6066e7d7b02.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.brainpickings.org/2014/10/16/the-history-manifesto-guldi-armitage/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2b7c3f7d-c764-4bf5-8aed-202936f71fff</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 18:40:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Laborers Who Keep Dick Pics and Beheadings Out of Your Facebook Feed]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Laborers Who Keep Dick Pics and Beheadings Out of Your Facebook Feed</h1><p>The campuses of the tech industry are famous for their lavish cafeterias, cushy shuttles, and on-site laundry services. But on a muggy February afternoon, some of these companies' most important work is being done 7,000 miles away, on the second floor of a former elementary school at the end of a row of auto mechanics' stalls in Bacoor, a gritty Filipino town 13 miles southwest of Manila.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e96d68b409f4633bcdac70d003ea4822946f9d4b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.wired.com/2014/10/content-moderation/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b94635ac-db97-46c6-99a1-690a348c75b0</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 18:40:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[frog]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>frog</h1><p>Without context, sensing data tells an incomplete story. As humans, we are driven to seek ever-deeper understandings of both the world around us and the world within us. A growing number of us do just that by tracking the hours we sleep, the calories we eat, the miles we run, and many other types of inputs, states, and measures of performance.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/43deff52b7351c62d1d012feccc03ac99db3fb4e.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://designmind.frogdesign.com/2014/05/qualified-self-going-beyond-quantification/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">52c1e5f7-775c-4d6a-98a9-4b1fe39425f9</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 18:40:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[frog]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>frog</h1><p>It is pretty clear that the role of objects is changing, and the way we interact with them is, too. We are still in control, but in a more cooperative and fluid way. We expect a lot from something that is labeled as smart.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b0d519911708e2d4c9902d40c5dcf39b3563918c.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://designmind.frogdesign.com/2014/10/when-objects-talk-back/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">67113524-78a7-40d9-b1f5-d64084f01b6f</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 18:40:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rethinking Segmentation for the New Digital Consumer]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Rethinking Segmentation for the New Digital Consumer</h1><p>Apple's launch this week of Apple Pay, its m-commerce product, could help finally move millions of mainstream consumers toward the promise of mobile payments, according to media reports. Given that Apple Pay will expose user preferences for payments and sharing data, this is a good time for companies to re-think how they segment their digital consumers, writes Mobiquity president Scott Snyder in this opinion piece.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/95392edcb8d2f2a56e838d24bad4a7836e2fc9de.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://knowledge.wharton.upenn.edu/article/bring-persona-rethinking-segmentation-new-digital-consumer/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f8179447-266a-4e85-853e-e2125af4c58f</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 18:40:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gamasutra: John Krajewski's Blog - 'You Have Died of Dysentery': How Games Will Revolutionize Education]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Gamasutra: John Krajewski's Blog - 'You Have Died of Dysentery': How Games Will Revolutionize Education</h1><p>What do you know about the Oregon Trail?  I’m willing to bet that your knowledge on the subject is gained almost entirely from the thusly-named game, where your typical quest across the country saw your resources dwindle, your family members drop one by one from accidents and disease, ending all too often with words ‘You have died of dysentery’. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e869521d69f7317c84f325b3204f149659e9484b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.gamasutra.com/blogs/JohnKrajewski/20140114/208612/You_Have_Died_of_Dysentery_How_Games_Will_Revolutionize_Education.php</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">883d477f-e2c7-405e-bace-32e73c3d3692</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 20:30:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>